<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-12-12T17:42:14+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Geeks’ things Korea</title><subtitle>The things and things to do in Korea Let’s just geek out for the another part that you could’ve missed.</subtitle><author><name>habni</name><email>habnipark@gmail.com</email></author><entry><title type="html">Welcome to GEEKS’ THINGS KOREA</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/description-of-geeks-things-korea/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to GEEKS' THINGS KOREA" /><published>2019-12-11T16:00:00+09:00</published><updated>2019-12-11T16:00:00+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/post01</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/description-of-geeks-things-korea/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;kcicking-it-like-a-geek-in-korea&quot;&gt;Kcicking it like a geek in Korea!&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/post/01/firstpic.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;mainpic&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;about-geeeks-things-korea&quot;&gt;About “Geeeks’ things Korea”&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;South Korea is small but there are so many various things to do, so more and more tourists are coming to Korea nowadays. Most of tourists are just visiting some particular places like Gangnam, Hongdae and Itaewon something like that. However there’s more and more things that you can enjoy here, but the point is it’s not that easy to find some informations about it for foreigners. Of course you can google it, but it feels like our professor “Google” always gives you the same and boring informations and recommendations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So that’s why I opened this website. I would like to show the real local things and something special than the other pages that you’ve searched so far. It could be something minor nothing like major things which travelers normally search for and do in Korea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’d like recommend you the things that I love to do, like shopping vintage stuffs, visiting old local bars, finding out some cool exhibitions, reviewing various stationaries and school things, taking pictures with film cameras and visiting photo studios to print that photos, trying to go on a bus trip, and so on.  So you can find something interesting through my posts and figure out “How Korean geeks enjoy their Korean lives”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I guarantee you that you can get more more ideas like ‘things to do in Korea’ from my page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/post/01/firstpic01.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;firstpic&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;about-contents-in-geeks-things-korea&quot;&gt;About contents in Geeks’ things Korea&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will post 2 types of things in Korea on ‘Geek’s things Korea’ homepage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*The things&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This category is about all things in Korea. so It could be some reviews, recommendations about the foods, products on Korean market, DIY kits, vintage antique stuffs that I bought and want to share with you… whatever.
 You will be able to read some reviews or recommendations and get informations from those so that you can also try for real.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*The things to do&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This category is about ‘the things to do in Korea’ but it will be totally different from another trip advise and recommendations because I will post somethings that even some local don’t know about. (maybe geek’s way to enjoy)&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Habni</name></author><category term="KOREA" /><category term="Thingstodoinkorea" /><category term="Koreatravel" /><category term="Koreatravelblog" /><category term="한국여행" /><summary type="html">Kcicking it like a geek in Korea!</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/%7B%22feature%22=%3E%22firstpostthumb.jpg%22%7D" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/%7B%22feature%22=%3E%22firstpostthumb.jpg%22%7D" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry></feed>